BACKEND SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Nahuel Brandán

EMAIL: contact@nahuelbrandan.com | WEB: nahuelbrandan.com

ABOUT ME 🔿

I am a Backend Software Developer, specialized in the **Python** ecosystem, with more than **3 years** of experience in the industry. Currently working for the aerospace sector.

I am passionate about turning ideas into functional products through software, going through the different stages of development and promoting good practices. Always in constant learning.

EXPERIENCE

BACKEND SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Company: Ascentio Technologies | Project: Sabia-Mar | 08/2021 - Present

Sabia-Mar is a satellite mission, with advanced technology for the study of the sea and the ocean, with the aim of providing valuable knowledge for the care of maritime resources and with an impact on the scientific and productive sectors.

I work as a software developer in **Python**, making contributions to different communication and flight planning modules of the satellite. Developer of both the software and the validation tests.

Working with technologies like: Robot Framework, Docker, FastAPI, Django, APIs.

BACKEND SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Company: IncluIT | Project: Junar Data Platform | 03/2019 - 07/2021

- Performing development activities in Python + Django + Django Rest Framework.
- Integration of Autho and Keyclok as a security layer to an API Management.
- Development related to **Elastic Search**, **Redis**, **Celery**.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER ANALYST

Faculty of Mathematics, Astronomy, Physics and Computing - UNC | 03/2014 - 10/2018

Career with strong emphasis on programming, analysis and design of systems, databases and computer networks, without neglecting the theoretical aspects that sustain them.

SELF-STUDY ONLINE COURSES | Platzi | 01/2021 - Actualidad

More than 100 courses completed and in constant learning in the Platzi professional online academy, on various topics such as: soft skills, english, software development, finance.

TECHNOLOGIES (

- Python
- Git
- C

- MongoDB
- FastAPI

- Github
- Autho

- Django

- API
- Flask

- MySQL
- Bash
- Redis
- DRF

- Linux
- Robot FW
- Elastic Search
- Docker
- Testing

EXTRAS C

• English: B1 intermediate

• Spanish: Native

HOBBIES





